<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aadi Shaktie</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_">
        647353297573-aefusmpi4ku1b94mum4n7gprmrgk5rj4.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="web_client">
        647353297573-p9rtbmg7p5nfhb8pjh9av9u3ordgdh3u.apps.googleusercontent.com
    </string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1401583893526903</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1401583893526903</string>

    <string name="a_rudraksha">
    A Rudraksha Welfare Foundation Initiative
    </string>

    <string name="devi_shakti">
    AADI SHAKTIE
    </string>

    <string name="astrology_n">
    Astrology | Numerology | Vastu Shastra |\nTarot Card | Lal Kitab
    </string>
    <string name="enter_your_details_to_create_a_new_account">Enter your details to create a new account</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="state_of_birth">State of Birth</string>
    <string name="city_of_birth">City of Birth</string>
    <string name="by_signing_up_you_agree_to_ourr">By signing up you agree to our  </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">  Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="amp"><![CDATA[ & ]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_policies">  Privacy Policies</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <string name="enter_your_">
    Enter your phone number to continue
    </string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="country_code">
    +91
    </string>

    <string name="enter_code_">
    Enter code sent to
        <!--        \n +91 9162715241-->
    </string>
    <string name="edit">(edit)</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="didnt">Didn’t receive? </string>
    <string name="reconnect">Reconnect</string>
    <string name="reconnect_text">Turn on your Wifi or Mobile Data to continue</string>
    <string name="disconnected">Disconnected!</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="languages">Languages</string>
    <string name="timings">Timings</string>
    <string name="timings_list">
        Monday: 10 AM to 5 PM\n\nTuesday: 10 AM to 5 PM\n\nWednesday: 10 AM to 5 PM\n\nThursday: 10 AM to 5 PM\n\nFriday: 10 AM to 5 PM\n\nSaturday: 10 AM to 5 PM\n\nSunday: 10 AM to 5 PM
    </string>
    <string name="background">Background</string>
    <string name="background_content">
        It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content of a page when looking at its layout.
    </string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="favourite_experts">Favourite Experts</string>
    <string name="calls">Calls</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="faq_s">FAQ’s</string>
    <string name="go_to_website">Go To Website</string>
    <string name="a_rudraksha_welfare_foundation_initiative">A Rudraksha Welfare Foundation Initiative</string>
    <string name="made_in_india">Made In India</string>
    <string name="logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="favorite_experts">Favorite Experts</string>
    <string name="upcoming_calls">Upcoming Calls</string>
    <string name="previous_calls">Previous Calls</string>
    <string name="review">Review</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="book_now">Book Now</string>
    <string name="what_next">What next?</string>
    <string name="creators">Creators</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email ID</string>
    <string name="basic_details">Basic Details</string>
    <string name="pooja_details">Pooja Details</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="time_slots">Time Slots</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="total_price">Total Price</string>
    <string name="same_as_whatsapp_number">Same as WhatsApp number</string>
    <string name="additional_information">Additional Information</string>
    <string name="done">DONE</string>
    <string name="congratulations_your_booking_has_been_confirmed">congrATULations...Your booking has been confirmed.</string>
    <string name="team_devi_shakti">Team Devi Shakti</string>
    <string name="know_the_creators_of_devi_shakti">Know the creators of “Devi Shakti”...</string>
    <string name="agora_app_id">e308b15a71e448b686d49256e0ce8e8f</string>
    <string name="agora_access_token">006e308b15a71e448b686d49256e0ce8e8fIABHk0TDlQu0yqpZLR5lrovGazqZwURvWiz5S2ZFmXn9n+IVUyEAAAAAEAA8nW45m78nYQEAAQCavydh</string>
    <string name="birth_details">Birth Details</string>
    <string name="hour">Hour</string>
    <string name="minute">Minute</string>
    <string name="seconds">Seconds</string>
    <string name="place_of_birth">Place Of Birth</string>
    <string name="create_kundali">Create Kundali</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="whatsapp_number">Whatsapp Number</string>
    <string name="your_account_is_under_review_status"> Your Account is under \n <u>REVIEW</u> Status!! </string>
    <string name="aadishaktiadmin_rudraksha_org_in"><u>aadishaktiadmin@rudraksha.org.in</u></string>
    <string name="diaclamer">“RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION”, got website(s): www.rudraksha.org.in and
www.devishakti.com along with their respective mobile based Applications “RUDRAKSHAA” and
“DEVISHAKTI”, developed and designed for general public benefits for offering services attached
with them at very economical rates in comparison to other available options in market during the
time these were being developed and designed by respective interns working with us. We along
with all associated Promoter, Employees and other related individuals does not represent or
endorse the accuracy, completeness, reliability of any advice, opinion, statement, or any other
information displayed, uploaded, distributed, linked through the website/ or its mobile
application named “DEVISHAKTI”. The user(s) of this website or Application (Android / Apple)
acknowledges that any reliance upon any such opinion, advice, statement, or information along
with soft-wares being used to provide such resolutions shall be at the user(s) risk. We don’t have
any liability of any sort being applicable on us or any of our associated Directors, Promoters,
Agents, Employee, Interns or marketing team or individuals. This disclaimer covers the both
websites and mobile Applications as associated with it as mentioned above.\n\n
We hereby specifies that we do not guarantee or warrantee the accuracy of any
information, advice, opinion, statement, or any other information displayed, uploaded,
distributed, linked through the website www.devishakti.com or its mobile application named
“DEVISHAKTI”. We also disclaim any or all warranties or fitness for a particular purpose or
merchantability or against infringement. In no event will “RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION”,
its employees, agents, or contractors, be liable to you for any damages or losses, including without
limitation indirect, consequential, special, incidental or punitive damages resulting from or caused
by the www.devishakti.com or mobile Application named “DEVISHAKTI”, (both Android / Apple)
its contents or any errors or commissions in its contents, even if advised of the possibilities of such
damages. The linked sites or mobile Applications (except www.rudraksha.org.in or mobile App
named “RUDRAKSSHAA”) are not under our control and “RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION”, is
not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site, or any
changes or updates of such sites. “RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION”, is providing these links
to the users only as a convenience and inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by us of
the site. We manage only www.devishakti.com and DEVISHAKTI mobile Application along with our
parent website www.rudraksha.org.in and mobile App “RUDRAKSHAA”. The information
presented at our parent website and its mobile Application will be regarding advertisement and
marketing purpose and same will be\n\n
Also by proceeding to the information beyond this notice, each user will be assuming all
the risks associated with the use of above mentioned website and mobile App, including risk of
your computer, software or data being damaged by any virus that might be transmitted or
activated via this site or your access to it. If you do not accept these terms, you should exit this
system immediately.\n\n
“RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION”, does not represent or endorse the accuracy,
completeness, reliability of any advice, opinion, statement, or any other information displayed,
uploaded, distributed, through the websites features message boards, sms / whatsapp chat and
email. The user acknowledges that any reliance upon any such opinion, advice, statement, or
information shall be at the user’s risk. The conversations, discussions, consultations done
regarding any sort of Astrological, Numerological, Vastu Shastra, Tarot Cards or Red Book between

subject matter experts and respective clients or any individuals will be done at their personal wish
and will and risk factor’s involved. We hereby will not be held liable for any sort of liability,
damages, and losses, risks etc. occurs or bound to occur for anyone involved in such conversations
for personal or professional benefits for self or anyone else, before, during or after such types of
conversations, discussions, and consultations. You are advised to follow such at your own wish
and will keeping in mind all sort of risks or damages involved. We will not be held liable to pay for
any sort of damages, losses, reimbursements, refunds etc. to any of the parties involved.\n\n
Confidentiality Disclaimer\n
“RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION” guarantees complete confidentiality of the members
identity, horoscope details and predictions. We also further guarantees that no direct or indirect
use will be made by it with respect to any aspect of life, as revealed in the horoscope of the
member, except for the explicit purpose of communicating the horoscope charts and predictions
to the concerned member. We might be using the data for teaching purpose in our sessions
regarding courses offered to general public in Astrology, Numerology, Vastu Shastra, Tarot Cards
and Red Book. The same will be done by keeping in view the secrecy of the individual’s name,
address, contact details etc. and will be used only as examples without disclosing the personal
details or references and will be presented as a case studies while teaching individuals or general
discussions regarding Astrology, Numerology, Vastu Shastra, Tarot Cards and Red Book.\n\n
Product Disclaimer\n
As we all know these Cosmic Sciences known as Astrology, Numerology, Vastu Shastra, Tarot card
and Red Book are based on predictions and assumptions which is being supported by the depth
and experience of the subject matter expert and trust in him/her of the respective party(s). It runs
on a basic rule that no one is always right and perfect as final outcome total depends as per the
wish and will of Supreme Power GOD. We know that while performing such actions, experts are
left out with their experience, wisdom, calculations, assumptions and faith and henceforth the
predictions done by them might happen in future.\n\n
We hereby strongly update all, that all types of recommendations provided by respective
subject matter experts like Astrological remedies, gemstones, palmistry predictions, Hawans,
Yagnas, any other types of ritual pujas or fasting etc. are based on their respective calculations,
predictions, experience, judgement and will have NO sort of liability over us. The experts provide
solutions, predictions, judgements, remedies might generally after having a detailed go through of
the Astrological chart of the individual in question (based on dob, time of birth and place of birth
details provided by individual), or as provided his or her date of birth (in case of Numerology),
Palmistry based solutions, (which are based on the ever changing lines of their palm), Vastu
Shastra remedies (based on the directions / other desired details of their properties etc.), Tarot
Cards (based on cards displayed while performing the readings), Red Book remedies (based on
Astrological chart, as based on above mentioned details). The overall outcome can be favourable
as desired by individual or might vary as it strongly depends on respective Karmas, actions of this
life as well as deeds done in previous births, as both cannot be judged by anyone, especially the
latter one in concern for any individual(s).\n\n

It must be clearly understood that every such prescription provided by any subject matter
expert to the concerned party or parties involved, is accompanied by a prescribed method and
procedure, which is expected to be followed by the member with due diligence. We “RUDRAKSHA
WELFARE FOUNDATION”, was, is and will not responsible for any claims for negative functioning
of any prescription of Astrological remedy made by any of our subject matter experts.\n\n
We update that all of our subject matter experts, tries to make their best efforts to
energize the gemstones or remedies provided in Astrology, Numerology, Vastu Shastra, Tarot
Cards, Palmistry and Red Book as per strict Vedic Principles as prescribed in ancient Vedic
scriptures, knowledge earned from various books, reading materials, literatures, self-experience,
other experts suggestions/ guidelines, online notes, other experts’ lectures and notes etc. We all
still have a strong need to understand that the final outcome will totally depend on wish and will
of Almighty GOD and we can only guide, assist and help based on our calculations and predictions
which further are dependent on all factors as mentioned above. We henceforth provides no
guarantees, implied warranties, or assurances of any kind, and will not be responsible for any
interpretation made or use by the recipient of the information and data mentioned above.\n\n
“RUDRAKSHA WELFARE FOUNDATION”, shall not be held responsible for the inaccuracies,
if any, in predictions. Any inadvertent reference to an individual, caste, creed, religion or any
spiritual path may be excused. The efficacy of any kind of remedies recommended in form of any
Astrological, Numerological, Vastu Shastra, Tarot Cards predictions, Red Book, Palmistry, Yantra,
Tantra, and Gemstones etc. will strictly depend on the faith and devotion of the customer and his
belief and intent. We and our experts requests and guides by default that one should wear
gemstones/ Yantras or perform any sort of rituals personalized/ community Yagnas/ Hawans only
when one has faith, true devotion and not out of any greed, fear or lust or any other negative
feelings. We do not offer any guaranteed results in the life of the customer for the
recommendation of any sort of remedies which was ever offered or is being offered or will be
offered by our subject matter experts to client or individual concerned.</string>
</resources>